My name's Greg Malik, live in the area here, Dyer.
I come to Phil's, love the place, love Eddie.
I've had my truck out here several times. He's made it look fantastic.
It always comes out cleaner, looking better than it did when I brought it in.
My wife's car just came out of here. She got it all fixed up.
Actually, we brought it over and sold it a couple of days later for a brand-new
car.
Okay.
And we got more money for it because it was looking good when we brought it there,
so it was an awesome time. We love the place.
We love the people that are working here. They are just fantastic.
Wait, so you had an accident?
Yes.
And then you brought it here.
Twice, yeah. I had two accidents. Other people hitting me.
Oh, other people hitting you.
Yes.
And then coming out of here-
It's always looking great
... it raised the value.
Oh, of my wife's. Hers we sold, yes.
It raised the value taking it out of here, so that we got more money at
the dealership for it. Then we got the new car.
Wow. So it sounds like you would say these guys are unique to other places.
The work is fantastic, and the people here are very unique.
They're always very comfortable. They take care of you.
Whether I call or just come in and talk, it's always a good time.
How did you find them?
I live right down the street.
Oh, okay.
So it was really easy. I saw it.
All right.
Came in the first time. Plus the insurance I use, State
Farm, they recommended coming here-
Okay
... the first time, so I've come in here ever since.
All right.